Murder is trending.
Spree is a comedy, crime, horror film directed by Eugene Kotlyarenko.
Desperate for an online following, a rideshare driver has figured out a deadly plan to
go viral and he will stop at nothing to get his five minutes of fame.
Kurt Kunkle, played by Joe Keery.
Jessie Adams, played by Sasheer Zamata.
Kris Kunkle, played by David Arquette.
Spree Rider, played by A.J. Del Cueto.
Spree Rider, played by Andy Faulkner.
Spree Rider, played by Honor Levy.
Spree is a 2020 American found footage black comedy
horror film directed by Eugene Kotlyarenko.
The gonzo-style satire follows a social media obsessed rideshare driver played by Joe Keery who, in an
attempt to become a viral trash-streamer, livestreams himself murdering passengers.
The film also stars Sasheer Zamata, David
Arquette, Kyle Mooney and Mischa Barton.
It was executive-produced by Drake.
Spree premiered on January 24, 2020, at the 2020 Sundance Film Festival as part of the NEXT category, and was
released theatrically and via video on demand in the United States on August 14, 2020, by RLJE Films.
The film received mixed reviews, though critics praised
Keery's performance and the film's premise.
The film explores themes of killing spree, found footage,
social media, ride-share, social media influencer.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and intense.